animeresimleri.com 2013-05-02

# Privacy Policy

animeresimleri.com Privacy Policy 

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy:

We use third-party advertising companies ( **Google Adsense** ) to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

animeresimleri.com strives to provide you with relevant and useful advertising programs such as Google Adsense. This program use the cookies, as well as other third party ad serving systems, to do so. They may use a range of information including cookies, web beacons, IP addresses, usage data and other non-personal information about your computer or device (such as browser type and operating system) to provide you with relevant advertising. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We collect information on what pages visitors visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page.

**With respect to cookies:** We use cookies to record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads.

**With respect to Ad Servers:** To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages.

**With respect to security:** We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

**Links**   
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information . This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site .
